Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications, Part 2
6007
U.S. Department of Labor
23 linear ft.
Records.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the number of publications in this collection the finding aid for it has been split into two.
The publications in Boxes 1 through 22 are listed in the container list of Part 1.
The publications in Boxes 23 through 27 are listed in the container list of this finding aid (Part 2).
SUBJECTS
Names:
United States.; United States. Dept. of Labor--Archives; United States. Dept. of Labor. Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation --Archives
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
CONTAINER LIST
- Shimada, Haruo's "Japan's" - Rewarding Work. (Box 23)
  - Shimada, Haruo, "Japan's Industrial Culture and Labor-Management Relations" (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Japan's Industrial Culture and Labor-Management Relations, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
      Author: Haruo Shimada
      Format: Publication
      Language: English.
  - Shimada, H., "Working Hours and the Distribution of Work--A Comment", Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Working Hours and the Distribution of Work- A Comment, 1978; Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Shioji, Ichiro, "Sound Cooperation Between Labor and Management", Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: Sound Co-Operation Between Labor and Management, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
      Author: Ichiro Shioji
  - Shipper, Frank, "Quality Circles Using Small Group Formation", Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles Using Small Group Formation, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
      Author: Frank Shipper
  - Shostak, Arthur B., "High Tech High Touch and Labor", Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: High Tech, High Touch and Labor, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
      Author: Arthur B. Shostak
  - Shumate, E. Chandler, Steven L. Dockstader and Delbert M. Nebecker, Performance Contingent Reward System: A Field Study of Efforts on Worker Productivity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Performance Contingent Reward System: A Field Study of Effects on Worker Productivity, 1978; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
      Author: E. Chandler Shumate, Steven L. Dockstader and Delbert M. Nebeker
  - Sibbersen, Richard D., "What Arbitrators Think About Technology Replacing Labor", Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: What Arbitrators Think aobut Technology Replacing Labor, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
      Author: Richard D. Sibbersen
  - Siegel, Irving H., Highlight of the Literature: Productivity Measurement: An Evolving Art, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Will Quality Circles Come Full Cycle?, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
      Author: Leon E. Siedel
  - Silvia, Stephen J. "The Social Charter of the Eur. Comm", Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: Productivity Measurement: An Evolving Art, 1980; Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Author: Irving H. Siegel
  - Simmons, John, "Frank Borman's Eastern Experiment", Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: The Social Charter of the European Community: A Defeat for European Labor, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
      Author: Stephen J. Silvia
  - Simmons, John and Geri Blitzman, "Training for Self-Managing Work Teams", Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Frank Borman's Eastern Experiment, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
      Author: John Simmons
  - Simpson, E.L., "Motorola's Participative Management", Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Training for Self-Managing Work Teams, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
      Author: John Simmons and Geri Blitzman
  - Sims, Arden C. et. al. "Does the Baldridge Award Really Work?", Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Motorola's Participative Management, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
      Author: E.L. Simpson
  - Sims, Henry P. Jr. and James W. Dean Jr., "Beyond Quality Circles: Self-Managing Teams", Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Does the Baldridge Award Really Work?, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
      Author: Arden C. Sims
  - Sims, Henry P. Jr. and Charles c. Manz, "Conversations with Self-Managed Work Groups", Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Beyond Quality Circles: Self-Managing Teams, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
      Author: Henry P. Sims, Jr. and James W. Dean, Jr.
  - Singer, Linda R. and Ronald A. Scheter, Mediating Civil Rights: The Age Discrimination Act, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Conversations Within Self-Managed Work Groups, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
      Author: Henry P. Sims, Jr. and Charles C. Manz
  - Singh, Ajit, "The End of the Golden Age, Global Economic Integration and Industrial Development in the North and South", Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Mediating Civil Rights: The Age Discrimination Act, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
      Author: Linda R. Singer and Ronald A. Schechter
  - Singh, Davinder, C. Glyn Williams and Ronald P. Wilder, "Wage Determination in U. S. Manufacturing 1958-1976: A Collective Bargaining Approach", Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: The End of the Golden Age, Global Economic Integration and Industrial Development in the North and South, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
      Author: Ajit Singh
  - Sink, D. Scott, "Total Quality Management is", Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Wage Determination in U.S. Manufacturing 1958-1976: A Collective Bargaining Approach, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
      Author: Davinder Singh, C. Glyn Williams, Ronald P. Wilder
  - Sizemore, William E. Esq., Potential Tort Liability in Employment, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Total Quality Management is, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
      Author: D. Scott Sink
  - Skelton, B.R., and Bruce Yandle, "Piece Rate Pay", Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Potential Tort Liability in Employment, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
      Author: William E. Sizemore
  - Skinner, Wickham, "The Impact of Changing Technology on the Working Environment", Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: Piece Rate Pay, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
      Author: B.R. Skelton and Bruce Yandle
  - Skinner, Wickham and Kishore, Chakraborty, Highlights of the Literature: The Impact of New Technology: People and Organizations in Service Industries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: The Impact of Changing Technology on the Working Environment, 1979; Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
      Author: Wickham Skinner
  - Skinner, Wickham and Kishore Chakraborty, Highlights of the Literature: The Impact of New Technology: People and Organizations in Manufacturing and Allied Industries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: The Impact of New Technology: People and Organizations in Service Industries, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
      Author: Wickham Skinner and Kishore Chakraborty
  - Slater, Phillip, and Bennis, Warren G. "Democracy in Investable", Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Highlights of the Literature: The Impact of New Technology: People and Organizations in Manufacturing and Allied Industries, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Slesnick, Don. "Critical Issues in the Health Care Industry", Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Democracy is Inevitable, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 26)
      Author: Phillip Slater and Warren G. Bennis
  - Smale, John G., "Corporate Takeovers: A Search for the Public Interest", Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Critical Issues in the Health Care Industry, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 27)
      Author: Don Slesnick
  - Smeltzer, Larry R., "Quality Circles--A Viable Productivity", Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Corporate Takeovers: A Search for the Public Interest, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 28)
      Author: John G. Smale
  - Smith, Clarence L., Final Report: Improving Local Government Productivity Through Application of Participative Methods Improvement Techniques, Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles- A Viable Productivity, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 29)
      Author: Larry R. Smeltzer
  - Smith, Craig, "Quality Circles come to California Local Government", Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Final Report: Improving Local Government Productivity Through Application of Participative Methods Improvement Techniques, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 30)
      Author: Clarence L. Smith
  - Smith, Deborah L. Wince. Perspectives on U.S. Technological Competiveness, Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Quality Circles come to California Public Employment, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 31)
      Author: Craig Smith
  - Smith, Judson, "A Trainer's Guide to Successful Productivity Improvement Planning", Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Perspectives on U.S. Technological Competitiveness, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 32)
      Author: Deborah L. Wince-Smith
  - Smith, Karl U. Ph.D. "Analysis of the Human Factors in Automation', Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: A trainer's guide to successful productivity improvement planning, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 33)
      Author: Judson Smith
  - Smith, Lee, "When the Workers are Bosses", Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Success Factors for Implementing Change, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 34)
      Author: Karl U. Smith
  - Smith, Michael J., Pascale Sainfort, Katherine Rogers, and LeGrande, David, "Electronic Performance Monitoring and Job Stress in Telecommunications Jobs", Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: When te Workers are Bosses, 1977; Publication (Box 23, Folder 35)
      Author: Lee Smith
  - Smith, Stuart, "New Structure Build Collaboration Among Teachers and Administrators", Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Electronic Performance Monitoring and Job Stress in Telecommunications Jobs, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 36)
      Author: Michael J. Smith, Pascale Sainfort, Katherine Rogers, and David LeGrande
  - Smith, Waldron P., "New in QWL: Employee Involvement That's Really Productive", Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: New Structures Build Collaboration among Teachers and Administrators, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 37)
      Author: Stuart Smith
  - Snyder, Kenton R., Elliott, Charles S. "Barriers to Factory Automation", Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: New in QWL: Employee Involvement That's Really Productive, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 38)
      Author: Waldron P. Smith
  - Social Science Research Council Advisory Group on a 1986 Quality of Employment Survey, Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Barriers to Factory Automation, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 39)
      Author: Kenton R. Snyder, Charles S. Elliott
  - Sockell, Donna, "The Legality of Employee Participation Structures Outside of Union Control", Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: America at Work: National Surveys of Employees and Employers, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Sockell, Donna, "The Legality of Employee-Participation Programs in Unionized Firms", Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: The Legality of Employee Participation Structures Outside of Union Control, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 41)
      Author: Donna Sockell
  - Soderland, Siv, Working Environment in Sweden: A Question of Partnership, Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: The Legality of Employee-Participation Programs in Unionized Firms, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Sokoloff, Kenneth L. and B. Zorina Khan, The Democratization of Invention During the Early Industrialization: Evidence from the United States: 1790-1846, Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Working Envrionment in Sweden: A Question of Partnership, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 43)
      Author: Siv Soderlund
  - Solberg, Sidney, "Changing Culture Through Ceremony: An Example from GM", Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: The Democratization of Invention During the Early Industrialization: Evidence from the United States: 1790-1846, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 44)
      Author: Kenneth L. Sokoloff and B. Zorina Khan
  - Solomon, Burt, "Ma Bell's Ambitious Kids", Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Changing Culture Through Ceremony, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 45)
      Author: Sidney Solberg
  - Sombrotto, Vincent R., "Employee Involvement: A Status Report", Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Ma Bell's Ambitious Kids, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 46)
      Author: Burt Solomon
  - "Some Fresh Ideas For Boosting Workers' Output", Publication (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Employee Involvement: A Status Report, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 47)
      Author: Vincent R. Sombrotto
  - Sonnenfield, Jeffrey A., Ingols, Cynthia A. "Working Knowledge: Charting a New Course for Training", Publication (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Some Fresh Ideas for Boosting Workers' Output, 1976; Publication (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Sorge, Arndt, "The Evolution of Industrial Democracy in the Countries of the European Community", Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Working Knowledge: Charting a New Course for Training, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 49)
      Author: Jeffrey A. Sonnenfeld, Cynthia A. Ingols
  - Soskice, David. "Industrial Relations and the British Economy, 1979-1983", Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: The Evolution of Industrial Democracy in the Countries of the European Community, 1976; Publication (Box 23, Folder 50)
      Author: Arndt Sorge
  - Spalter-Roth, Roberta and Heidi Hartmann, Raises and Recognition: Secretaries, Clerical Work and the Union Wage Premium, Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: Industrial Relations and the British Economy, 1979-1983, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 51)
      Author: David Soskice
  - Special Supplement: Americans with Disabilities Act, Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Raises and Recognition: Secretaries, Clerical Workers and the Union Wage Premium, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 52)
      Author: Roberta Spalter-Roth and Heidi Hartmann
  - Spector, Bert, "Training Leadership: The New Challenge for U.S. Unions", Publication (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Special Supplement: Americans with Disabilities Act, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Spector, David Ritter, David Insurance Coverage of employee Claims Against Employers, Publication (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: Training Leadership: The New Challenge for U.S. Unions, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 54)
      Author: Bert Spector
  - Spencer, Daniel G., "Employee Voice and Employee Retention", Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: Insurance Coverage of Employee Claims Against Employers, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 55)
      Author: David Spector and David Ritter
  - Spillane, Robert, A.W. Findley and Kerry Borthwick, "Perceptions of Worker Participation: The Influence of Job Status and Political Affiliation", Publication (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: Employee Voice and Employee Retention, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 56)
      Author: Daniel G. Spencer
  - Speirs, Joseph "A Coming Surge in Capital Spending", Publication (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: Perceptions of Worker Participation: The Influence of Job Status and Political Affiliation, 1982; Publication (Box 23, Folder 57)
      Author: Robert Spillane, A.W. Findlay and Kerry Borthwick
  - Spiers, Joseph "The Baby-Boomlet is for Real", Publication (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: A Coming Surge in Capital Spending, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 58)
      Author: Joseph Spiers
  - Spiller, Rex and Thomas J. Housel, "SMR Forum: Video Teleconferencing-A New Training Tool", Publication (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: The Baby Boomlet is for Real, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Spivey, Allen Lawrence, Thomas Global Management: Concepts, Themes, Problems, and Research Issues, Publication (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: SMR Forum: Video Teleconferencing- A New Training Tool, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 60)
      Author: Rex Spiller and Thomas J. Housel
  - Spizman, Lawrence and James Cicarelli, "Unions, Politicians, and Public Interest: Retrenchment in the Public Sector", Publication (Box 23, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: Global Management: Concepts, Themes, Problems, and Research Issues, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 61)
      Author: W. Allen Spivey and Lawrason D. Thomas
  - Spring, H. Charles Remarks at the Symposium of CB in Industrialized Market Economy Countries, Publication (Box 23, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Unions, Politicians, and the Public Interest: Retrenchment in the Public Sector, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 62)
      Author: Lawrence Spizman and James Cicarelli
  - Springer, Beverly J. "1992: The Impact on Compensation and Benefits in the European Community", Publication (Box 23, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the United States: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 63)
      Author: H. Charles Spring
  - Standing, Guy, "The Notion of Technological Unemployment", Publication (Box 23, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: 1992: The Impact on Compensation and Benefits in the European Community, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 64)
      Author: Beverly J. Springer
  - Stanley Foundation, International Agenda for the 1990's: 23rd UN of the Next Decade Conference, Publication (Box 23, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: The Notion of Technological Unemployment, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 65)
      Author: Guy Standing
  - Starr, Martin and Nancy E. Bloom, The Performance of Japanese-Owned firms in America: Survey Report, Publication (Box 23, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: International Agenda for the 1990's: 23rd UN of the Next Decade Conference, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - State and Local Government Labor-Management Committee "Controlling Public Employee Health Care Costs Through Labor-Management Committees", Publication (Box 23, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: The Performance of Japanese-Owned Firms in America: Survey Report, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 67)
      Author: Martin Starr and Nancy E. Bloom
  - Staw, Barry M., "Organizational Psychology and the Pursuit of the Happy/Productive Worker", Publication (Box 23, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Controlling Public Employee Health Care Costs Through Labor-Management Committees, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Stein, Barry, "Quality of Work Life in context: What Every Practitioner Should Know", Publication (Box 23, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Organizational Psychology and the Pursuit of the Happy/Productive Worker, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 69)
      Author: Barry M. Staw
  - "Steel Seeks Higher Output Via Workplace Reform", Publication (Box 23, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: Steel Listens to Workers and Likes What it Hears, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Steele, Lowell W. and N. Bruce Hannay, The Competitive Status of U.S. Industry, Publication (Box 23, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: Steel Seeks Higher Output via Workplace Reform, 1980; Publication (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Steele, William, "Owners and Operators", Publication (Box 23, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: The Competitive Status of U.S. Industry- An Overview, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 72)
      Author: Lowell W. Steele and N. Bruce Hannay
  - Stein, Barry A. and Rosabeth Moss Kanter, "Building the Parallel Organization: Creating Mechanisms for Permanent Quality of Work Life", Publication (Box 23, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: Owners and Operators, 1983; Publication (Box 23, Folder 73)
      Author: William Steele
  - Stein, Leslie Reicin Esq. The Employment Provisions of the Americans With Disabilities Act, Publication (Box 23, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Building the Parallel Organization: Creating Mechanisms for Permanent Quality of Work Life, 1980; Publication (Box 23, Folder 74)
      Author: Barry A. Stein and Rosabeth Moss Kanter
  - Stein, Peter M. and Peter S. Gray, "Truth in Drug Testing", Publication (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: The Employment Provisions of the Americans with Disabilities Act, 1992; Publication (Box 23, Folder 75)
      Author: Leslie Reicin Stein
  - Steiner, Robert E., "The Labor-Management Cooperation Act", Publication (Box 23, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: Truth in Drug Testing, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 76)
      Author: Peter M. Stein and Peter S. Gray
  - Steinnes, Donald N., "Business Climate, Tax Incentives and Regional Economic Development", Publication (Box 23, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: The Labor-Management Cooperation Act, 1981; Publication (Box 23, Folder 77)
      Author: Robert E. Steiner
  - Stephens, Elvis C., "Why Courts Overrule Arbitrators' Awards", Publication (Box 23, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Business Climate, Tax Incentives and Regional Economic Development, 1984; Publication (Box 23, Folder 78)
      Author: Donald N. Steinnes
  - Stephens, R.A. (Tony) "Connecting with Customers", Publication (Box 23, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Why Courts Overrule Arbitrators' Awards, 1985; Publication (Box 23, Folder 79)
      Author: Elvis C. Stephens
  - Stepp, John R., Approaches to Improving Productivity in the United States, Publication (Box 23, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: Connecting with Customers, 1991; Publication (Box 23, Folder 80)
      Author: R.A. (Tony) Stephens
  - Stepp, John R., "Emerging Trends in Labor-Management Relations", Publication (Box 23, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Approaches to Improving Productivity in the United States, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 81)
      Author: John R. Stepp
  - Stepp, John R., "The Future of Labor Relations and collective Bargaining", Publication (Box 23, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: Emerging Trends in Labor-Management Relations, 1986; Publication (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Stepp, John R. and John L. Bonner, "Stats Tie Economic Development to Improved Labor Relations Climates, Publication (Box 23, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: The Future of Labor Relations and Collective Bargaining, 1990; Publication (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Stepp, John R., "Global Competitions: The Role of Industrial Relations", Publication (Box 23, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: States Tie Economic Development to Improved Labor Relations Climates, 1987; Publication (Box 23, Folder 84)
      Author: John R. Stepp and John L. Bonner
  - Stepp, John R., "Hardware, Software and Humanware", Publication (Box 23, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Global Competitions: The role of Industrial Relations, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 85)
  - Stepp, John R., "Keynote Remarks: Collective Bargaining Directions in the 90's", Publication (Box 23, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Hardware, Software, and Humanware, 1989; Publication (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Stepp, John R., "Labor-Management Cooperation: A Framework for Economic Development", Publication (Box 23, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Keynote Remarks: Collective Bargaining Directions in the 90's, 1988; Publication (Box 23, Folder 87)